好了 找到你们了
Okay. Found you.
头等舱有一个空座
I do have an open seat in first class,
如果你们其中一人愿意免费升舱的话
if one of you would like a free upgrade.
不用了 谢谢 我们要坐在一起
No, thank you. I think we'll sit together.
在我们度过了美满的周末后
After the amazing weekend we just had --
给我吧
I'll take it.
那座位是我应得的
I deserved that seat.
和菲尔的前拉拉队死党们
Three days in the woods with
在丛林里共度了三天
Phil's ex-cheerleader buddies --
听老掉牙的故事
the old stories,
看他们自发地叠罗汉
the spontaneous human pyramids,
还不停地在Tumblr上发翻跟头的照片
constantly updating their tumbler Tumblr --
我全程陪笑
I smiled through the whole thing.
但问题是我演得太好了
Problem is I was so convincing,
菲尔觉得我是真的很开心
Phil thought I was having a great time.
我想要什么呢 颁个奖吧
What do I want? Some credit.
什么时候要呢 就现在吧
When do I want it? Now.
很抱歉我一身营火味
I'm sorry if I smell like a campfire.
我在丛林里待三天了
I've been in the woods for three days.
我讨厌野营
I hate camping.
我要是在丛林里待了三天
If I'm ever in the woods for three days,
那意味着我已经死了两天了
it means I've been dead for two of them.
发自内心地笑感觉太好了
It feels good to laugh for real.
你看起来需要喝点酒啊
You look like you need a drink.
亲爱的
Hon?
给我的朋友拿两杯霞多丽和一条热毛巾
Two chardonnays and a hot towel for my friend.
马上来
Right away.
我爱你 陌生美女
I love you, beautiful stranger.
不得不承认 我有点生气
I have to admit, I was a little miffed
克莱尔居然选择了好座位
that Claire grabbed the good seat,
特别是我刚给她制造了一个魔幻般的周末
especially after I gave her such a magical weekend,
但我决心要保持乐观
but I was determined to stay positive.
之后我突然想到[打中了我]
And then it hit me.
各位 萨尔到了
Everybody, Sal's here.
-好了 -好了
- Okay. - All right.
条幅"直"吗
Is this straight?
你办一个迎婴派对
You're throwing a baby shower
邀请了十几个穿着定制西裤
with a dozen men in tailored pants
喝着贝里尼酒的男人
sipping Bellinis.
完全看不出哪里...我都说不出口了
Nothing about this is -- ugh, I can't even finish.
怎么 最后一个词分量太重了吗
Really? The last word was too much?
我们决定把死党们聚集起来
So, we decided to get the gang together
给我们的朋友萨尔办一个迟来的迎婴派对
to throw our friend Sal a belated baby shower.
她最近比较忙
She's been a little hard to pin down lately,
但我们知道她肯定不愿错过
but we knew she'd never miss the chance
一帮汉子一起送礼[洗澡]的机会
to shower with a bunch of men.
你很爱这个梗是吧
You love that joke, don't you?
因为那是一词多意
Well, because it's two different kinds of showers.
这是小萨米
This is little Sammy.
这也是第一次
This is as long
你来我们家这么久没喝酒
as you've ever been in our house without a cocktail.
不了 谢谢 请给我水就行
No, thank you. Just a water, please.
各位 别这么吃惊
Okay, everybody, drop your pearls.
我还在母乳喂养呢
I'm still breastfeeding.
书上都说 至少母乳喂养一年
All the books say, "Do it at least a year."
约坦 这杯你喝吧
Jotham, drink this.
不行 我得提早离开去看冰球赛
I can't. I'm leaving early to go to a hockey game.
国王对阵黑鹰[音似"黑屌"]
Kings versus Blackhawks.
队名还能叫这个吗
They can call a team that?
黑 鹰
Black hawks.
我要把这个放到厨房去
I've got to put this in the kitchen.
所有宝宝食物都是我自己做的
I make all my own baby food.
完全天然 无化学添加
It's all-natural, no chemicals.
这个女人是谁
Uh, who is this woman?
她不喝酒 自己做婴儿食物
She's not drinking, she's making her own baby food.
莉莉还有别的盘子吗
Does Lily have any other plates?
我不能让萨米从塑料餐具里吃饭
I don't let Sammy eat off this plastic.
另外那边的橱柜里
Uh, yeah, the far cabinet.
完全说不通啊
Okay. None of this makes sense.
我知道 她不让宝宝碰塑料的话
I know. How does she breastfeed him
她要怎么母乳喂养啊[硅胶]
if she doesn't let him near plastic?
妈 我发烧了吗
Mom, do I have a fever?
我看看
Ay, let me check.
我们有体温计啊
You know, we have a thermometer.
你一定要总是这么白人作风吗
Do you have to be so white all the time?
宝贝 快去躺下
Oh, baby, go lay down.
你真是个勇敢的小男孩
You're such a brave, little boy!
他装的
He's faking it.
他装病
He's pretending to be sick
为了不去上烹饪课
so he doesn't have to go to his cooking class.
他必须得去 今天教做千层面
He has to go. Today's lasagna.
我饿了一天就等那个了
I've been starving myself all day for that.
他不想去
He doesn't want to go
因为那里有个孩子总捉弄他
because there's a boy there that is picking on him.
烹饪课吗
Cooking class?
我们都不知道能送他去哪里
You know, we're running out of places to send him
他会是酷学生了
where he can be cool.
我知道 真的是够了
I know. Enough is enough.
你得教他打架
You have to teach him how to fight.
对 这管用
Yeah. That'll work.
你去教他
You're doing this.
但别告诉他这是我的主意
And don't tell him that this is coming from me.
知道他妈妈觉得他软弱对男孩子不好
It's bad for a boy to know that his mother thinks he's weak.
会让他变成那种花钱找女人
That's a lifetime of paying women
打他屁股的男人
to spank him until he cries.
那孩子天生不会打架
The kid is just not a fighter.
他砸牛肉都小心翼翼的
He gets squeamish pounding veal.
教他
Just do it!
好吧 但我教他只是为了千层面
Fine, but I'm only doing it for the lasagna
还有他每周日带回来的食物
and the extra food he's been bringing home on Sundays.
这样周一就方便多了
Makes Mondays easier, you know?
天呐 你真是加菲猫
Oh, my God, you're the Garfield.
两位美女有谁愿意
One of you pretty ladies
一会儿带我去见一个妹子吗
want to take me to meet a girl later?
你觉得叫我们美女就有免费车坐吗
You think calling us pretty is gonna get you a ride?
我来吧
I'll take it.
你要走的时候告诉我
Let me know when you want to leave.
另外 我喜欢罗思 我觉得她很配你
Besides, I like Rose. I think she's good for you.
是另一个姑娘 莎拉
This is a new girl -- Sarah.
我受够罗思了 她很神经
I'm done with Rose. She crazy.
慢着 花花公子
Easy, Macklemore.
你说"神经"是什么意思
What do you mean, "crazy"?
我告诉你他什么意思
I'll tell you what he means.
女人在任何方面挑战了男人
Any time a woman challenges a man in any way,
她就成了神经病
suddenly, she's crazy.
她做了什么神经病的事 卢克
So, what did she do that was so crazy, Luke --
跟你说了她的建议吗
Give you her opinion?
是啊 或者 她竟敢谈她的感受
Yeah, or what, did she dare to talk about her feelings?
听起来你们好像是懂我了
The words sound like you get it,
但你们的口气却像在批评我
but your tone is throwing me.
拜托告诉我你分手时说了几句好听的
Just tell me you said something nice when you broke up with her.
我还没跟她分手呢
I haven't broken up with her.
什么
What?!
打电话给别人
It just seems weird
告诉他们坏消息 感觉有些奇怪
to call someone up and give them bad news.
她总会知道的
She'll find out somehow.
你什么时候成了男人 好恶心
Ugh. Ugh, when did you become a guy? It's gross.
你得勇敢地面对她
You need to stand up and face her.
当面吗
In person?
我们30岁了吗 给她发短信啊
What are we, 30? Send her a text.
你得温柔地告诉她
You need to break it to her gently.
首先 告诉她她超棒
First, tell her she's awesome.
而且好漂亮
And pretty.
如果她超棒而且漂亮
If she was awesome and pretty,
我根本不会甩了她
I wouldn't be dumping her.
照做 你个蠢猪
Just do it, you pig.
我们都知道我不会那样做
We all know I'm not gonna do it,
如果你们想要这样 给
so if you want it done, here.
别偷窥我的手机
Oh, and don't go looking around on there.
不会让你们更喜欢我的
It's not gonna make you like me more.
抱歉 我觉得你坐了我的位置
's-scuse me. I think you're in my seat.
先生 我们觉得你坐了她的位置
Sir, we think you're in her seat.
不 我绝对是坐16C
No, I'm definitely 16c.
这是19C
This is 19c.
该死 应该是往前三排
Oh, darn it, that's three rows up.
对不起
Sorry about that.
没事
That's all right.
欢迎
Hi. Welcome.
你能等会儿再坐吗
Um, could you hang back a second?
我手机掉了
I-I dropped my phone.
我也许有你想找的东西
I may have, uh, what you're looking for...
-在这里 -等等 什么
- Right there. - Wait. What?
你好 我是职业魔术师
Hi. I'm a professional magician.
老天爷啊 你是爱德华·罗格朗
Holy sword-box, you're Edward LeGrand.
是的 正是在下
Yeah, I am. I am.
我是菲尔·邓菲
I-I'm Phil Dunphy,
职业房地产经纪人 业余魔术师
p-professional realtor, amateur magician.
-很高兴认识你 -你好 我是吉莉安
- Well, nice to meet you. - Hi. I'm Jillian.
别人说我有魔法之手
I've been told I have magic hands.
我是按摩师
I'm a masseuse.
你为什么一直揉前臂
Why do you keep rubbing your forearm like that?
-有个行李箱砸到我了 -让我看看
- Oh, I-I had a suitcase land on me. - Oh, let me see.
菲尔
Hey, Phil... ohh.
我有个新魔术想表演给你看
...I've got a great new trick I want to show you.
我也可以表演魔术
Oh! Ooh, I can do tricks, too.
这地方联系着你的舌头
This spot's connected to your tongue.
需要我帮你放好包包吗
Can I stow your bag for you?
不 我们会需要的
Mm. No, we'll be needing this.
八卦杂志
Trashy magazines.
你最好了
Oh, you're the best.
焦糖巧克力
Ooh. Caramel truffles.
我还多带了一个松软的颈枕
I even brought an extra fluffy neck pillow.
母亲的拥抱肯定就是这种感觉
Oh, this must be what a mother's hug feels like.
喂
Hello?
看来她把你照顾得很好
Well, it looks like she's taking good care of you.
她是我最好的朋友
Well, she is my best friend.
听我说 胡里奥
Listen to me, Julio.
我要你今天清理好水沟 不是明天[西语]
I want the gutters cleaned today, not manana.
如果人们都认为我们国家的人很懒
If everyone thought my people were lazy,
我会尽一切努力表现得勤奋
I would do whatever it took to not seem lazy.
明白了吗
Comprende?
实际上我们很快就要起飞了
Actually, we're gonna take off soon,
所以我们需要你关掉手机
so we're gonna need you to turn off your phone.
我还没说完呢 再来两杯
I'm actually not done talking, and two more.
如果我是你
Well, if I were you,
我会放下玉米煎饼 爬上梯子
I'd put down the burrito and get up that ladder.
你怎么还站在这里
What are you doing standing there
不给我和我的闺蜜克莱尔拿酒啊
and not getting drinks for me and my good friend, Claire?
实际上我们刚见面
Actually, we just met.
两位
Oh, guys, guys,
我不能让你们俩打扫
I can't let you do the cleanup all by yourselves.
罗纳多会帮忙
Ronaldo will help you.
当然啦
Of course!
萨尔在哪里
Uh, where is Sal?
我需要她的钥匙 好把礼物搬上她的车
I need her keys to start loading the gifts in her car.
她好像在我们房间里给萨米换尿布
I think she's changing Sammy in our room.
希望她把窗帘也换了
I hope she's also changing those drapes. Oh!
我不想听起来像是个多愁善感的人
I don't want to sound like a sentimental softy,
但有谁想念
but does anyone miss
过去的那个醉婊子吗
the drunken whore she used to be?
我喜欢新的萨尔
Oh, I like the new Sal.
原来只需要一个小宝宝 她的母性本能
Turns out, all she needed to bring out her maternal instinct
就焕发出来了
was a little baby.
我不信 不 有什么不对劲
I don't buy it. No, something's up.
你记得她建议我们把莉莉淹死在海里吧
You do remember her suggesting we chuck Lily into the ocean.
米奇尔 冷静点 宝宝会让人改变
Oh, Mitchell, calm down. Babies change people.
你以前是个愤世嫉俗的评判者
Like you used to be a judgmental cynic,
然后莉莉... 等等
and then Lily -- oh, wait.
萨尔没在那里
You guys, Sal's not back there.
-萨尔 -窗帘还在
- Sal? - The drapes still are.
真奇怪 她的车不见了
Well, that's weird. Her car's gone.
什么
What?!
别太快下结论
Let's not jump to conclusions.
在这片地区 她的车可能是被偷了
In this neighborhood, her car could have been stolen.
她看起来的确有些疲惫
Well, you know, she did seem frazzled.
也许她忘记说再见了
May-- maybe she forgot to say goodbye.
忘了她的所有礼物吗
Oh, and forgot all of her presents.
忘了她的宝宝
And forgot her baby.
你们不会觉得她...
You don't think that there's any way that she would --
不
N-no.
我都说不出口
I-I can't even say it.
我可以
I can.
女酒鬼抛弃了私生子
That gin-soaked tart abandoned the little bastard.
干什么 他没有父亲
What? He's fatherless.
我说错了吗
Am I wrong?
我给萨尔打了五次电话
Okay, I've called Sal five times,
她还是没接
and she still hasn't picked up.
我就知道"大地母亲"什么的是一场戏
I knew this whole "Earth mother" thing was an act.
当我们指责一位母亲
Oh, maybe we should use our happy voices
抛弃了她的小宝宝时
when we're accusing a mommy
我们也许该用快乐的声音
of abandoning her little baby boy.
-这真是一场灾难 -不是吗
- Ugh. This is a true disaster. - Isn't it?
有人把西班牙式屋顶
Someone put a Spanish roof
盖在了中世纪农场式别墅上
on what is clearly a mid-century ranch.
不好
Oh, no.
有人刚拉屎了
Someone just went numero two.
余震依然绵绵不断
And the aftershocks are still rolling in.
这是她的尿布包 这是...
Here's her diaper bag. And...what's --
等等 这里有张字条
Oh, no. This, here's a note.
很抱歉以这样的方式离开
"I'm sorry to leave this way.
我并不感到自豪
I'm not proud of it,
但我真的受不了了
but I just can't do this anymore.
再见 萨尔
Goodbye. Sal."
越来越难
It's getting harder and harder
不把这事往坏处想了
to keep a positive spin on this.
吃点奶酪吧
Here. Have some cheese.
不了 谢谢 我不吃
Oh, no. Thank you. I’m, I’m good.
天呐
Oh, my.
这味道还真重
That is strong.
天呐
Oh, my goodness.
看什么看
Hey. What are you staring at?
这可是法式奶酪
It's French cheese.
你一周的薪水都买不起
Costs more than you make in a week.
你最好小声点
Okay, you might want to keep your voice down.
-克莱尔 -怎么了
- Claire. - Yeah?
那边的帅哥在对你放电
That guy over there is checking you out!
我觉得他不是
I don't think he is.
我朋友克莱尔想在卫生间和你相会
My friend Claire would like to meet you in the bathroom.
我没那么说
No. I-I did not say that.
克莱尔 你为什么要这样糟蹋自己
Claire, why do you do that to yourself?
你这么漂亮
You are so pretty.
菲尔 几点了
Hey, Phil, what time is it?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我的手表不见了 爱德华
My watch is gone, Edward,
你做了什么
what did you do?
吉莉安 你中间名的开头是什么
Jillian, what's your middle initial?
C 代表凯瑟琳
"C," For Catherine.
菲尔 你第一次跟女生接吻是什么时候
And, Phil, what age were you when you first kissed a girl?
12岁和表妹 14岁和不是表妹的女生
12 cousin, 14 non-cousin.
从不是表妹的那个算起吧
Let's stick with non-cousin.
如果你去到那边的14C座位
I think if you go to 14c, seat right over there,
你会找到你想要的[上发条]
you'll wind up with what you're looking for.
我的表是电池表
It works on battery,
不过我好激动
but, oh, my God, I'm excited!
借过
Excuse me.
-菲尔 是我 -是你啊
- Phil. It's me. - Oh, hey.
-你在这做什么 -我需要逃离
- What are you doing back here? - I need a break
坐在我旁边的那个女人
from the woman I'm sitting next to up there.
-她是世界上最糟糕的人 -真遗憾
- She is the worst person on earth. - I’m sorry.
我想她对你可能不会这么咄咄逼人
I was hoping she might be a little less aggressive with you.
你愿意跟我换一下座位吗
Do you mind switching with me for a little while?
亲爱的 你不会想跟我换的
Oh, honey, you don't want to.
这里简直是地狱
It's hell back here, too.
我左边坐着一位胖女士
I'm squished between this fat lady
一直撞到我的胳膊肘
who keeps digging into my elbow
右边坐着一位汗津津的老兄
and this huge, sweaty dude
一直拿自己的工作夸夸其谈
who won't stop blabbing on about his job.
能抱一下我吗 我需要一个拥抱
Well, could I get a hug? I could really use one.
没问题 他们让我们回座位了
Sure thing. They want us back in our seats.
我没听到提示声啊
I didn't hear the little ding.
你肯定是耳塞了
Your ears must be plugged.
感觉到了吗
Did you feel that?
什么都没感觉到
No, I-I-I didn't feel anything.
太恐怖了 你还是回去吧
This is scary. You should go back.
太棒了
Amazing.
谢谢
Thank you.
大魔法师
Sorcerer!
还不错 感受到你的力量了
Not bad. I felt that one.
很不错 曼尼
So good, Manny.
这次再用力点
All right, really let one go this time.
想想那家伙让你多么生气
Thinks about how mad this guy makes you.
-他叫什么 -吉迪恩[犹太勇士]
- What's his name? - Gideon.
天呐
Oh, geez.
想想他对你做了什么
All right, think about what he did to you.
我还是不说了
I'd rather not talk about it.
不知道你傻笑什么 你的茴香都糊了
I don't know why you're smiling. Your fennel's burnt.
我的奶油南瓜汤就要大功告成了
Whereas I made a perfect butternut squash.
你拿的只是黄油而已
That's just butter.
我忘了我要做的是奶油蛋蛋汤
Oh, yeah, I-I totally forgot the nut squash!
用力 用力 不错
Snap it. Snap it. Good.
-再来啊 -够了
- More. Good. - I’m done.
不打了 不值得
I'm not fighting anymore. It's not worth it.
但你做得很棒啊
But you're doing so good.
就是要先把肩膀转过来
You just have to turn your shoulder first
这样出拳时就能把全身的重量一并送出去
so that you can throw your weight behind your punch.
如果你想的话
If you want.
我觉得你已经很威猛了
I already think that you're very tough.
这都是杰的主意
This is all Jay's idea.
好了 继续 让他们看看谁是猛男
All right. Come on, kid. Show them who's boss.
不 比起斗殴 我更喜欢走慈爱路线
No. I'm more of a lover than a fighter.
反正我的目标是这个
Well, that's the goal, anyway.
宝贝 你开心就好
Okay, papi, whatever you decide.
不要让他离开这个房间
Don't let him leave this room!
也许该由你来教他
Maybe you should teach him how to hit.
天呐 看这个
Oh, my God. Check it out.
罗思收到了你的分手短信 给了回复
Rose got your breakup text and wrote back.
她发火了
She mad.
怎么发火了 把手机给我
What? Give me that.
谢谢你发来史上最蠢的分手短信
"Thanks for the dumbest breakup text ever.
不要夸一个女孩很棒 然后跟她分手
Don't call a girl awesome, then break up with her.
如果我那么好 你为什么还要甩了我
If I'm so great, why'd you dump me?
别自以为是了 冷血的禽兽
Get over yourself, you insensitive troll"?
她是什么毛病 怎么能这样跟你说话
What is her problem? She can't talk to you like that.
不 她是在跟你们说话
She's not. She's talking to you.
真不敢相信我原来还挺喜欢她
I can't believe I ever liked this girl.
我们的短信深情又礼貌
Our text was compassionate and respectful.
哪里蠢了
There was nothing dumb about it.
百分之一百万
A million percent.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
那个贱人惹到我这个贱人真是失误
This crazy bitch just messed with the wrong crazy bitch.
这不是真的
This is unreal.
我们都知道萨尔有点疯疯癫癫
We always knew Sal was unstable,
但她怎么能做这种事
but how could she do this?
我们还不知道她做了什么
We don't know that she's done anything.
假设她现在坐在一架
Okay, let's just suppose for a second
去往卡波的飞机上
that she's on a plane to Cabo.
然后呢
What then?
也许这一切是命中注定
Maybe this is part of a bigger plan.
也许在莉莉之后
You know, maybe the reason
我们没有领养别的孩子
we didn't adopt another baby after Lily
是因为上帝想让我们收养萨米
was because god wanted us available for Sammy.
这个上帝不让我们领养孩子
Who is this god that denies us a baby,
却让一个狂野女怀了孕
then gets a party girl pregnant,
最后抛弃自己的孩子
only to have her desert the baby
好让我们能收养他
so that we can finally get one?
就是这个上帝让处女怀孕
The same god that impregnated a virgin,
让摩西在篮子里顺河漂下
sent Moses down the river in a basket,
让亚伯拉罕杀死自己的儿子
and commanded Abraham to stab his own son.
上帝总是对小孩不太好
God only does weird baby stuff.
好吧 我承认
Okay, yes, I'll admit,
其实我也想留下这个小家伙
there is part of me that would love to keep this little guy
像萨尔装出来的那样抚养他
and raise him the way Sal was pretending to.
没错 也可以给莉莉添个小弟弟
Exactly. Lily could have a baby brother.
但还有制度管着呢
But there are systems in place here.
你总不能把他当作
You can't just keep him
一只院子里捡到的兔子留下吧
like a bunny you found in the yard.
那也太扯了
That's crazy.
听着 我们讨论过了
Listen, we discussed it,
我们觉得孩子应该给我们
and we think we should take the kid.
我们该给他取啥名
What should we call him?
不确定 但肯定不能叫萨米
Not sure, but definitely not Sammy.
萨米·萨尔茨曼听起来蠢爆了
Sammy Saltzman sounds so silly.
可以用上手洗牌法
We can overhand shuffle,
也可以用鸽尾洗牌法
and we can riffle shuffle...
但你知道吗
But, you know,
无论如何都躲不开暴怒的
there is no escape from the angry...
-皇后 -什么
- Queen. - What?
菲尔 你在干什么
Phil. What are you doing?
苦中作乐
Making the best of a bad situation?
那女的为什么要揉你肩膀
Why is that woman rubbing your shoulders?
吉莉安是位按摩师
Oh, uh, Jillian is a masseuse,
这位就是大名鼎鼎的爱德华·罗格朗
and this, of course, is Edward LeGrand.
见到你很高兴
Pleasure to meet you.
能把黑桃A还我吗
Now, if you could just give me my ace of spades back,
就在你口袋里
it's in your pocket.
原来你那么着急回到这个地狱般的座位
This is why you had to race back to your hellish seat --
是为了享受背部按摩和纸牌魔术啊
for back rubs and card tricks?
你知不知道我旁边坐着个什么人
Do you have any idea what I'm going through up there?
那女的剪了自己的脚趾甲
She clipped her toenails
因为她的"亚洲女人"手法不对
because her "Oriental girl" didn't do it right.
克莱尔 抱歉
Claire, I'm sorry.
但你得检查下口袋
But I need you to check your pocket.
我去
Insanity!
谢谢您
Thank you very much.
别生我的气啊
Don't be mad at me.
是你自己要坐在那的
You're the one who grabbed that seat.
你那么做真的很自私
That was a pretty selfish move.
没错 是我要坐在那的
Yeah, I did grab that seat,
因为整个周末我都大公无私
because I spent the entire weekend being selfless,
但你都没谢过我
and you didn't even thank me once.
我为什么要谢你
Why would I thank you
我给了你一个超棒的周末
for giving you an awesome weekend?
超棒
Awesome?
你整个周末都在重温
You spent the whole weekend rehashing stories
阿痒 阿锈还有爱爱船的故事
about itchy, rusty, and loveboat.
我怎么可能会觉得这些东西有趣
How is that fun for me?!
这些梗都超好笑好吗
They were always getting into stuff!
我过来想找点安慰
I came back here for some compassion,
你却对我撒谎 把我撇在一边
and all you did was lie to me and blow me off
跑回来接着享乐
so you could keep having your fun
我却只能坐在头等舱煎熬
while I suffer up there in first class!
我好同情你
Oh, my heart goes out to you.
去你的吧 克雷斯金[算命大师]
Oh, stick it, Kreskin.
老娘旁边坐着个吃奶酪的种族歧视者
I'm sitting next to a cheese-eating racist.
对不起 你的牌被撕了
I'm sorry about your card.
不用
Don't be.
我的...
Son of a...
到了
All right.
我六点回来接你
I'll be back -- pick you up at 6:00.
还记得我怎么教你的吗
Now, remember, what did I teach you?
暴力能解决一切
Violence solves everything,
还有别像大力水手似的挥拳
and don't wind my fist up like Popeye.
不是暴力 是自卫
It's not violence. It's self-defense.
你不能任他欺负你
You cannot let this kid keep pushing you around.
给我拿出一副恶棍样 走进去
Now, you walk in there like a badass,
做出人所未见的美味千层面
and you make the best damn lasagna anybody's ever seen.
谢谢您的教导 杰
I appreciate the speech, jay,
但我会按照我的方式来处理这事
but I'll handle things my way.
孩子 还有一件事
Kid, one more thing.
别忘了大蒜面包
Don't forget the garlic bread.
-要是没了它 -我懂
- Because without that... i- - I get it.
等等 迪尔加多
Hey, Delgado.
曼尼 我跟你说话呢
Manny, I'm talking to you.
想要一块这个吗[想打架吗]
You want a piece of this?
你这是干嘛
Ow! What was that for?
看来是你被我打了
Looks like I gave you a piece of this.
你有病啊
What the hell?
我刚问你要不要烤苹果奶酥啊
I was just offering you some apple crumble!
什么 才不是呢
What? You were not.
我说真的 上次的事我很内疚
Yes, I was! I felt bad about teasing you.
我的心理医生说
My therapist said
我行为失常是因为父母离婚
I was acting out because of my parents' divorce,
所以我想跟你和解
so I was trying to be nice.
对不起 我不知道
I'm so sorry. I didn't know!
打得好
Good shot, kid!
现在知道别招惹谁了吧 小混球
That'll teach you who to pick on, you punk --
离他远点
Not my boy!
他的拳法可是跟高手学的
He learned how to punch from the best.
他父母要离婚了
His parents are getting divorced,
他做了那些甜点来道歉
and he made me that dessert as an apology.
这全都是你妈的主意
This whole thing was your mother's idea.
罗纳多 你拿上那个会摇的东西
Ronaldo, you grab the roller thingy, and, uh --
我拿那个网眼笼
Oh! I'll grab that big mesh cage.
够了 所有人都停手
All right. Everybody, stop.
你不能就这么收养一个孩子
You can't just keep a baby
跟在院子里捡到的兔子似的
like it's some rabbit you found in the yard.
有制度管着呢
There are systems in place.
他今晚总得待在什么地方吧
He has to stay somewhere tonight, no?
没错 待在这不行吗
Yeah, how about right here,
我们可是有育儿经验的
because we know how to raise a child?
得了吧
Oh, please.
我们会给他换衣服 喂他吃东西
We'll dress him and feed him,
粑粑什么的可以让肯奇塔处理
and Conchetta can handle the poopy stuff.
我给她上了医疗保险呢
I gave her Obamacare.
这点事她总该做吧
It's the least she can do.
我们都想给宝宝最好的
We all want what's best for the baby.
你们人不错 但我们有经验
Y-you're very nice people, but we've done this before.
那又怎样 该轮到我们了
So? It's our turn.
我想要孩子很久了
I wanted a child for some time now.
人家身体马上就不适合养了呢
My biological clock is ticking.
您这说辞也太扯了呢
That's the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard.
-扯吗 我44了 -你才44也挺扯的
- Is it? I'm 44. - Or that is.
你个牙尖嘴利的小婊砸
You are one mean lady.
没费利佩我们决不走
We're not leaving without Felipe.
行 那你们就留在这吧
Well, then, you're not leaving.
留就留
Fine!
真的要叫"费利佩"吗
Did we settle on "Felipe"?
菲尔
Phil.
宝贝 你在这干嘛
Honey, what are you doing?
你等下
One second.
我衣橱里有20件皮毛大衣
So, I have 20 fur coats in my closet,
但我的朋友里面
but I'm the only one of my friends
只有我还会穿那些
who even wears them anymore,
你说说到底是谁要绝种了
so you tell me who's endangered.
吉莉安在我的座位等着
Jillian's waiting for you in my seat
为你做个背部按摩
to give you a little back rub.
你没必要这么做
You don't have to do this.
你这个周末也没必要那么耐心
You didn't have to be so great this weekend.
但你做到了 谢谢你
But you were, so thank you.
我应该更早一些感谢你的
And I should have said that earlier.
去享受剩下的旅程吧
Go enjoy the rest of your flight.
这边交给我处理
I'll deal with this.
"交给你处理"
"Deal with this"?
我可是州议员的情妇
I'm a state senator's mistress.
你是我的英雄
You're my hero.
进屋前把鞋底蹭干净
Wipe your feet before you come in!
听听 她说的第一句话
Listen to that. First thing out of her mouth,
就是给我们下命令
she's telling us what to do.
一切都要在今天结束
Well, that stops today.
我们要强势一点 决不让步
We go in strong. We hold our ground.
要让她知道 我们不再随她摆布了
We let her know she's done pushing us around.
曼尼 你怎么这么早就回来了
Manny, why are you home so early?
你让他翘课吗
Did you let him skip school?
不是 妈
No, mom.
我被开除了
I was kicked out
因为我打了一个被误解的学生
for punching a really misunderstood kid,
都是因为你
thanks to you.
因为我吗 什么
Thanks to me? What, did --
我都告诉他了
I told him everything.
你知道我们意识到了什么吗
And you know what we realized?
我们的生活中的确有个欺凌弱小的人
There is a bully in our life,
就是你
and it's you.
你给我们定规矩 随意指使我们
You make the rules, you boss us around,
-我们不会再忍气吞声了 -没错
- and we're not gonna take it anymore. - Mm. Yeah.
瞧瞧你们两个
Ah, look at you two,
鼓足勇气 来和这个
standing up to the big, scary bully
爱你们 保护你们
that loves you and protects you
希望你们安全的大坏蛋对峙
and wants you to be safe in this world.
现在你们在我眼中就是两个渺小的男人
You're just tiny, little men to me right now,
给我离开这个房子 带着敬意回来
and you need to leave this house and come back with more respect!
还有比萨饼
And a pizza.
怎么
Oh, what?
你们要先去看看睫毛膏有没有花掉吗
You need to go first and check on your mascara?
-我们的确需要吃东西 -是的
- We do need to eat. - Yeah.
吃比萨饼挺好
I wouldn't mind some pizza.
不要上面带菠萝的
We're not getting any pineapple.
要带菠萝的
You are getting pineapple!
我们把菠萝都挑出去
We're taking it off our slices.
不要浪费食物 杰
Don't waste any food, Jay!
我觉得我们表明了立场
I think we made our point.
完全表明了
Totally.
我们自己买比萨饼去 在车里吃
We'll get our own pizza -- eat it in the car.
给我一个理由
Give me one reason
为什么萨米今晚应该留在这里
why Sammy should stay here tonight
而不是跟我们走
instead of with us.
因为我们有做家长的经验
Because we're experienced parents.
我们有婴儿床
We have a crib!
我们有私家儿科医生
We have a pediatrician.
我们的家对宝宝很安全
Our house is babyproofed.
我们的家被《建筑设计文摘》拍摄过
Our house was in Architectural Digest.
罗纳多 省省吧 说那个没用
Ronaldo, please, you're not helping.
他们根本没听过那本杂志
They don't know what that is.
你们这个蜗居怎么可能再容下一个孩子呢
How can you even fit another child in this shoe box?
你们太穷了
You're poor!
我们有栋漂亮的房子 还有个大院子
We have a beautiful house with a big yard
他可以在那里和园丁一起玩球
where he could throw the ball with the gardener.
好吧 听着
Okay, look.
如果有人要收养萨米 那一定是我们
If anybody's gonna adopt Sammy, it's gonna be us.
都不问一下我的意见吗
Whoa! Do I have any say in this?
萨尔 你回来了
Sal! Oh, well, you're back.
你们四个在干什么呢
What the hell are you four doing?
你离开了派对
You walked out of here
什么都没说就把宝宝扔下了
and left your baby without saying a word,
所以也许应该由我们来问你
so maybe we'll be asking the questions.
我跟约翰·约翰说了我要去哪里
I told John John where I was going.
派对上醉得最厉害的那个家伙
The drunkest guy at the party.
抱歉我不想打断
Excuse me for not wanting
你们的激烈辩论
to interrupt your fierce debate --
威猛先生和那个
"Who's hotter,
厕纸包装上印的肌肉男谁更帅
Mr. Clean or the brawny paper towel man?"
-威猛先生 -厕纸肌肉男
- Mr. Clean. - Brawny paper towel guy.
不要再吵起来了
We're not going back there.
这还是不能解释你为什么忽然离开
That still doesn't explain why you would leave
你自己的迎婴派对
in the middle of your own baby shower.
约坦提起黑鹰队的时候把我吓到了
I got freaked out when Jotham mentioned the Blackhawks.
每次 每次我都听错
Every time. I hear it every time.
萨米的父亲是那个球队的
Sammy's dad is on the team, okay?
他不知道萨米的存在
And he didn't know Sammy existed --
至少在刚刚我跑过去告诉他之前
At least not until I just went down there
他不知道
and I told him.
天呐 怎么样 他的反应如何
Oh, gosh. What happened? How did he take it?
原来他是有妇之夫
It turns out he's married.
是的 我本可以先在网上查一下他的
Yeah, I could have googled that.
所以他指不上了
So he's out.
你们觉得我抛弃了自己的宝宝吗
And you thought I deserted my own baby?
你的确离开了
You did leave.
还有 这个纸条又是怎么回事
And then what -- what's up with this note, huh?
很抱歉以这样的方式离开
Look -- "I'm sorry to leave this way.
我并不感到自豪 但我实在受不了了
I'm not proud of it, but I just can't do this."
这个尿布包
This diaper bag
是以前我单身时用过的包包
is just a recycled purse from my single days!
里面有很多这样的纸条
I got a lot of these notes lying around
以便我迅速甩掉男人们
for quick getaways.
你们觉得养孩子这事我做不来 是不是
You guys don't think that I can do this, do you?
不是
No!
-我们一直觉得你能行 -我可没有
- We always thought you could do it. - I certainly don't.
-我们不认为你做不到 -闭嘴
- We don't think you can't do it. - Shut up!
我自己也不认为我能行
I don't think I can do it, either!
萨尔
Oh, Sal.
实在
I mean, it's just
太艰难了
so hard.
他没有爸爸 让我觉得好内疚
I feel so guilty that he doesn't have a dad in the picture.
我不知道 我努力把每件事做得完美
I don't know. I'm trying to do everything perfectly.
感觉好累
It's exhausting.
而且我有一年没有滚床单了
And I haven't had sex in like a year.
这个小家伙
This little dude --
是我生命中唯一一个不能搞砸的事
He's the one thing in my life that I cannot mess up.
我只是希望能给他一个父亲
I just wish I could give him a dad.
我们怎么样
Well... what about us?
我们可以做萨米的爸爸 我们所有人
We could be Sammy's dad. All of us.
是啊 萨尔 我们爱你
Yeah, Sal, we love you,
我们永远支持你 无论你需要什么
and we're always here for you -- whatever you need.
除了七月我们要去卡普里岛
Except we'll be in Capri all of July.
说真的 萨尔
Seriously, Sal,
你和萨米永远都不会孤单
you and Sammy will never be alone.
你们真好
You guys are so sweet.
等等 六月也不行
Wait. June's no good, either.
我要去整一下我的脖子
I'm getting my neck done.
天呐 你们干了什么
Oh my god. What did you do?
我们维护了你的尊严
We stuck up for you.
没错 罗思自找的
Yeah. Rose had it coming.
她怎么能像我们那样跟你讲话
She can't talk to you the way we do.
罗思把你们的短信转发给了莎拉
Well, Rose forwarded your texts to Sarah.
现在莎拉不愿意跟我约会了
And now Sarah doesn't want to go out with me.
把手机给我
Give me that phone.
那个贱人莎拉说什么了
What did the skank Sarah say to you?
哎哟 开头不错
Yeah ouch. Good opening.
真幽默 是我们自作自受
So funny. We totally deserve that.
没错 这小姑娘真幽默
Totally. Good sense of humor.
-天呐 爱死她了 -我也是
- Oh my god. I love her. - Me too.
别担心 卢克 我们会把她追回来的
Don't worry Luke. We're gonna win her back.
我们只需...
We're just go...
卢克
Luke!
我们是不是应该去找自己的约会对象
You think maybe we need dates of our own?
太需要了
So bad.